[Juliette panting]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[gasps]
[grunts. groans]
Stop.
[alarm blaring]
[alarm continues blaring]
[grunts]
[grunts. sniffs]
[groans]
Carl?
[citizens clamoring]
Please stay inside. Your Honor.
What's going on?
The sheriff didn't clean. ma'am.
[automated voice] Return to your homes
as quickly and quietly as possible.
Your safety is our only concern.
Return to your homes
as quickly and quietly as possible.
Your safety is our only concern.
Return to your homes as
quickly and quietly as possible.
Nichols went over the hill.
- I know.
- I couldn't find you.
I called in the alarm.
Scrambled the off-duty
and the reserved raiders.
Good. Announce
an 8:00 p.m. emergency curfew.
putting the sheriff's deputies
under your command.
I also need eyes on Nichols's father.
Don't harass him.
Just see who he's talking to
and who talks to him.
Sending Nichols out to clean
was supposed to prevent this.
I will be making a speech later today.
Do you hear what's going on?
People are saying
it's time for another rebellion.
That's why they need to know
what happened today.
It's under investigation.
We're talking to everyone
who knew Nichols.
I know what happened.
There are two people in the Down Deep
I need detained.
Take them into custody.
Bet they're loving this down there.
- [citizens clamoring]
- [Hank] Hey!
People. let's calm down.
Let's calm down. Please. Quiet.
Listen to me.
[automated voice] Return to your homes
as quickly and quietly...
No. you can't cut off
official announcements!
Your safety is our--
[citizens cheering]
Hey! No. Come on. move it out.
Come on.
I don't make the rules.
[citizen 1] Hank. fuck you!
I just watched. the same as you.
She walked over the hill.
- That means it's safe.
- [citizens murmuring]
- I wanna go out too.
- [citizens clamoring]
Don't say that. You can't say that.
Please calm down. You can't say that.
[Knox] Move.
Hank. give it up.
- You're in over your head.
- [citizens] Yes!
You need to shut the fuck up
and listen to these people.
[citizens] Yes!
- We got a right to ask questions.
- [citizens] Yes!
- Don't we?
We just saw something no one
has ever seen before.
- And we all want to know what that means.
- [citizens] Yes.
Juliette Nichols was one of our own.
Then why'd you turn her in?
I did.
Jules is like family to me.
but I had to make a choice.
They knew she was here.
They'd have torn our homes apart.
They're just looking for an excuse.
They think we're dumb animals.
We have to show them--
They'll think different after we cut off
the power and shut down the Silo.
- [citizen 2] Yes!
- [clamoring]
Once!
We can shut the Silo down once.
And then they'll crush us.
We all saw Jules walk over the hill.
We're not gonna listen to lies anymore.
We want the truth.
[clamoring]
[Knox] Listen to me!
Listen.
[water spraying]
[citizens gasping. groaning]
Most of us got jobs to get back to.
don't we?
[citizens coughing. murmuring]
[Knox] You gotta stop.
This place is a tinderbox.
Is that an order?
Yes.
[Alice] Doctor?
Dr. Nichols?
The Anderson baby won't stop crying.
[baby crying]
[Pete] How'd you do this. little one?
[Alice] What?
[Pete] She dislocated her elbow.
[baby continues crying]
There you go.
All done.
Do you want me to...
Poor little girl.
[grunts]
- [crying stops]
- [sighs]
[babbling]
Poor little girl.
You're serious.
The Sheriff's Department reports to you?
For now. It's only temporary. Paul.
And we're getting
the sheriff's apartment cleaned out.
Bernard wants you and your family
to move in there as soon as possible.
He wants things to get back to normal.
She walked over the hill.
How are things going to be normal?
By us. All of us acting coolly and calmly.
Are there any other parts of the Pact
Bernard plans on ignoring?
[Sims] Paul. this is an emergency.
Am I still supposed to write
my report on Nichols's cleaning?
Of course.
I still haven't gotten your statement.
Nichols saying she wanted to go out.
All right. here's my statement.
Bernard believed Nichols was
in violation of our relic laws.
He led her to the cornfield
to keep her arrest non-disruptive.
Once he confronted her about
the red-level relic in her possession--
A relic he later destroyed.
For the safety of the Silo.
Once he confronted her. which I observed.
Nichols said she wanted to go out.
As raiders came in
to apprehend her. she ran.
They chased her and caught her.
End of statement.
That do it?
[Paul] One thing.
If Nichols just said
she wanted to go out. why did she run?
I don't know.
She must have changed her mind.
What if she's still alive?
[sighs] We can't just sit here when
she might still be out there somewhere.
She's not alive.
There's only so much air in that suit.
What was the note
you had me deliver to her?
I figured you'd read it.
Of course. I read it.
I-- I just-- I didn't understand it.
You weren't supposed to.
Just a private joke
between me and my girl.
You said they're good in supply.
Is that about the tape?
[inhales sharply] Why don't you leave
me alone to feel like shit for a while?
I'm sorry. Walk.
But...
it's not enough to just mourn.
[knocking]
Hey. Shirl.
[sighs] What do you want?
I need to talk to Walker alone.
Go on.
How you doing?
How the hell do you think I'm doing?
Yeah. Yeah. dumb question. Sorry.
Look...
I'm sorry. Walker.
But Judicial Security has
some questions they want to ask you.
They know where to find me.
I'm. uh. supposed to
take you into custody.
Sheriff's Department
works for Judicial now?
As of an hour ago. Yes.
You gotta come with me. Walk...
And. uh...
I need to make it look good.
[scoffs]
[Meadows] It's not possible.
They all say they won't clean
and they all do.
Your Honor. I saw it.
She-- She held out the cleaning pad
and then she just dropped it.
- But then it got--
- What? Did she decide not to die too?
She walked over the hill.
[Meadows] I don't believe you.
Everybody saw it.
Go. please.
[door opens]
[door closes]
What now. Bernard?
[breathes sharply]
I thought we told you scum
from Mechanical to stay out of here.
Good to see you. you son of a bitch.
I missed you.
Heard some crazy shit about your shadow.
They must be pissed off up top.
[Knox] Yeah.
they're coming down on everybody.
[disabled worker] Fuck 'em.
They need us more than we need them.
[Knox] Feels different this time.
Yeah. it does. But you'll handle it.
You're your old man's son.
Sometimes I'm not sure if
that's a good thing or a bad thing.
Trust me. it's a good thing.
Hadn't been for him.
I'd never have made it out.
I need some help.
Okay. If I can.
I got two asks.
If anybody comes to you
and wants you to make weapons. don't.
It's too dangerous.
What's the second ask?
[knocking]
[Bernard breathes deeply]
You must know why I'm here.
More or less.
[sighs]
[Bernard breathes deeply]
I'd make you a drink.
but I don't want you to stay that long.
Understood.
Uh. feel free
to have one yourself. if you like.
I stopped.
You stopped?
[Meadows] Mm-hmm.
Hmm. When?
Today.
Oh. [scoffs]
[inhales sharply]
I'm speaking to the Silo this evening
and I would like you to be behind me.
Behind you?
As a show of unity.
to reassure the people.
But you're not ordering me.
Well. with the lives
of 10.000 people at risk.
I didn't think I'd have to order you.
I came here myself to ask. out of respect.
Do you know how she got over the hill?
It had to be the tape.
Someone was gonna figure
that out sooner or later.
My mistake was not sending
Nichols to the mines when she stole it.
[breathes sharply]
You're frightened.
Well. no one knows me better than you.
[Meadows] So. do you imagine
that an angry mob
is gonna break down the door
and kill us all?
I'm not afraid of what I imagine.
I'm afraid of what I saw.
What she saw.
On the other side of that hill.
Thousands and thousands of bodies.
An entire silo dead.
It looked like the Silo
went to war with itself.
That's what scares me.
Because if it happened there.
it could happen here.
Your beloved Order lays out the protocols.
For what to do if someone fails to clean.
But The Order doesn't say anything
about what to do
if someone walks out of fucking sight.
The Founders never imagined it
or wouldn't admit it was possible.
But today it happened.
and the entire Silo watched it happen.
So. what are you gonna do?
Well. that's what I'm here for.
to figure it out.
Well. I can't help you.
[Bernard] You were my shadow.
- And then I wasn't.
- [Bernard] This is an emergency.
[scoffs]
I'll never fucking understand you.
What was it. Mary?
Twenty-five years of a secret.
What are you holding on to?
What aren't you telling me?
You're hiding something.
Well. I need your help and. uh.
if you're not willing to do it
for old times' sake
and you're not willing
to do it for the Silo.
then what is it you fucking want?
More living space?
The pick of the relics?
A bigger staff? What the fuck do you want?
[sighs] You still don't know me. do you?
All right then.
I'll tell you what I'll settle for.
[Meadows] In this story.
there is an all-powerful wizard
who no one ever sees.
And when they do.
he turns out to be a fraud...
hiding behind a handful of cheap tricks.
So I'm a fraud?
No. I am.
And at the end of the story. he gets
into a hot-air balloon and he flies away.
That's what I want.
Can you do that for me?
Because if you can.
well. then I'll help you.
But if you can't...
well. then fuck off.
[citizens chattering]
I hate to do this to you.
but... [sighs] ...I gotta lock you up.
What in hell's going on. Hank?
Since when do you lock up old ladies?
Since I got orders to hold you
both for questioning by Judicial.
You need anything.
holler until somebody comes.
Where are you going?
[Hank] Oh. we gotta go make sure
everybody's out to hear
the mayor's speech.
First they want them all
staying inside their apartments.
now they want 'em outside.
Come on. Here. let's go.
So. what did you tell 'em?
Not a damn thing.
I thought you said something.
You know me better than that.
Hank locked her
in the deputy station holding cell.
McLain's there too.
It's gotta be about the tape.
The IT tape Jules stole was shit. right?
I think Walker and McLain must have
switched it out with our heat tape.
Wait. wait. you think Judicial
knew the suit tape didn't work?
[Shirley] They had to.
If we can get to Walk.
find out what she knows. we'll have proof.
But why would people believe Walker
instead of Judicial?
Because they just saw Juliette
walk over the hill.
- [Martha] The deal is--
- I have a plan.
Judicial may suspect we did it
but they can't know for sure.
Not about you.
But that tape comes right back to me.
- Maybe. But--
- [Carla] No buts.
Juliette came to me.
begged me to switch the tape.
You had nothing to do with it.
[Martha] No. no. Hell with that.
We keep our mouths shut.
make them tell us
what they think happened.
Then we deny everything.
They know it was the tape.
[Martha] We're the only two people
who know that for sure.
Keep our mouths shut.
We got a chance to brass it out.
You old fool.
They don't need us to tell them anything.
They'll find some lowlife to denounce us
and send us both
to the mines or out to clean.
The only chance we got to box 'em in.
is for me to cop to it.
I'm damned if I'm gonna watch them
punish you for something I started.
Then they'll kill us both.
That's gonna happen. sooner or later.
Least this way. we get to go together.
[Bernard clears throat]
I know many of you are feeling uncertain
or unsettled by what you saw
earlier today.
But I am here to tell you
that today was a good day.
Today was the first day of a new era.
For as long as we can remember.
everyone that went out to clean.
died on that hillside.
Killed by the dangerous toxins
of an unsafe world.
But today. that changed.
Sheriff Nichols asked to go out.
Sheriff Nichols went out.
She chose not to clean.
- She's a traitor.
- No. she was not a traitor.
Juliette Nichols was a fighter.
I disagreed with her about many things.
but I respected her.
And never more so than I did today.
She's alive.
No.
No. I wish that were true...
I really wish it were.
But she died a hero to the Silo.
- [crowd murmuring]
- It's impossible.
Do you all want to listen
to these gentlemen yell?
Or do you want to hear
why Juliette was a hero?
[murmuring continues]
Before she went out...
I asked Sheriff Nichols
if we could seal her suit
with a new kind of tape.
A tape recently developed
by our brilliant suit technicians.
And she--
she courageously agreed.
Her trip over that hill
proved that our new tape
provided better protection
against the dangers outside.
And that is the first step forward
in our lifetime.
[cheering. applauding]
And we are not finished.
We will keep finding ways
to make our suits better and stronger.
And to produce tape that may someday
protect all of us
from the dangers outside
and bring us closer to our ultimate goal
of safely leaving the Silo.
[cheering. applauding]
I'd like to thank the mayor
for this exemplary new development.
and commend him
for his decisive leadership
at this critical time.
[crowd murmuring]
[Meadows] I hereby decree.
by the powers given to me by the Pact.
five credits be bestowed
upon every household
to celebrate this great achievement.
[crowd cheering. applauding]
[Meadows] We can only hope
that this new tape will lead to a new day
for each and every one of us.
They're lying.
Juliette discovered that IT
was using bad tape on purpose.
This isn't new tape.
this is the good tape we use.
And they didn't plan to use it.
someone from Mechanical switched the tape.
- The mayor's lying.
- [raider] Hey!
- What's your name?
- Juliette Nichols.
[citizens cheering. applauding]
- Come with me.
- [Knox] What's the problem?
- She's one of my people.
- [raider] She's under arrest.
- You need to step back.
- Oof. whoa.
This your first time below 120?
I'm Knox.
I can promise you.
she's not a troublemaker.
She's just having a bad day.
She lost a friend and she's been drinking.
but she's one of the best techs
in the Silo.
This deputy will vouch for her.
Hank?
I'm trying to explain how I can't afford
to lose Shirley right now.
Yeah. we'll keep an eye on her.
She'll be home before curfew.
[raider] That mouth of hers
will get her sent to the mines.
[Knox] Thank you. I owe you.
I'd say you both do.
Come on. We need to talk.
We have nothing to talk about.
Fuck.
Follow her.
We. uh. threw in a couple of extra lines.
just to make it look real.
And you've been paid fairly for it.
You need us again. you say the word.
Until I do. keep your mouths shut.
Or you won't just go back to detention.
Okay. I took care of the hecklers.
They were good. by the way.
Nice job.
[Sims] Thanks.
Do you know what it is?
I do.
Was it important?
No. but it is now.
What's the mood like out there?
Any incidents?
[Sims] People are back in their homes.
No violence reported.
Deputies are all with us.
Watchers have eyes on known troublemakers.
You turned it around.
For now.
[Sims] You know you don't have
to do this alone.
If I was your shadow. I could make sure
we would be okay and--
The speech bought us a day. maybe two.
Crisis is not over.
I need you right where you are.
Now. I'd better go.
Wouldn't wanna violate my own curfew.
I didn't forget about you.
Sorry you had to miss the mayor's speech.
[inhales heavily]
- You...
- [lock clanging]
...are free to go.
You got 30 minutes till curfew. Go on.
You said Judicial had questions.
[Hank] Yeah. They had questions earlier.
and now they don't.
At least the mayor explained
how Juliette walked over the hill.
What'd he say?
[Hank] It's a new kind of tape
IT just came up with.
Come on.
Thank you.
- [raider 1] Mr. Mayor.
- [raider 2] Mr. Mayor.
Thank you for your service.
Sorry I'm late.
Anthony asleep?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. he asked where you were.
I said. "I guess
Daddy doesn't love us anymore."
Honey. I'm kidding.
Sorry. I'm so tired I'm punchy.
and it's gonna be like this
till the emergency's over.
Here.
I'll heat up your dinner.
Thanks.
Did you have a chance to talk to Bernard?
I asked him straight-out. and he said
I was too valuable where I was.
At least for now.
The man needs a shadow.
Even if it's not me.
We both know it should be you.
It has to be you.
What is he waiting for?
I'm trying to figure that out.
[Camille] Did you know Meadows
was gonna be there today?
I didn't.
And nobody's been able to tell me
why she was there.
Hmm.
I can't remember the last time
she made an appearance.
Sure caused a big stir.
Did you work with her
when you were in Judicial?
[scoffs] She didn't even know I was alive.
But they said she was in IT
before she moved to Judicial.
Did Meadows and Bernard
know each other back then?
[Camille] Yeah. possibly.
He was already head of IT. Why?
[Sims] I told Bernard he didn't
have to handle this alone.
and he didn't seem concerned.
Which makes me think
maybe he wasn't handling it alone.
You think h-he's talking to Meadows?
[clicks tongue] I don't know.
There was something about
the way he looked at her today.
You're still full of surprises.
Come in.
Thank you for your endorsement.
What changed your mind?
To be honest.
I went there to watch you fail.
To watch it all fall down around you.
And?
[inhales deeply]
I never thought
you had any talent for politics.
But in light of today's performance.
I could be wrong.
[scoffs] I wasn't bad. was I?
- I assume the hecklers were arranged for?
- [inhales deeply]
Yeah. you don't wanna leave
anything like that to chance.
And I think the cover story works.
[Meadows scoffs] Works?
It's ludicrous.
But given the situation.
it does what you need it to do.
I approached it like an equation.
[stammers] People saw a miracle happen.
and if I tried to tell them it didn't.
some would buy it
but the mob saw what it saw.
So. I gave them a story to explain
the two different kinds of tape.
Now. if anyone tries
to tell a different story.
then they have to disprove mine.
[inhales deeply] And if that doesn't work.
there's always brute force.
Mm-hmm.
Brute force works for a while. but--
But what?
You need to give them
something to believe in.
That is why I need you.
[Meadows] You don't need me.
You proved that today.
On my way up here.
I saw the same new graffiti three times.
"JL."
And that was up here.
Who knows what's happening
in the Down Deep?
The speech bought us a few days.
but I can't manage this crisis
without you.
Because I'm the only other person
who's been in that vault.
Because you're the only other person
that I will listen to.
I tried to find another shadow. but...
[sighs]
You set the bar too high.
Listen. when I asked
for your help earlier.
I offered you incentives and bribes.
and I--
I realize that was insulting.
And patronizing.
And I. uh--
I-I-- I apologize.
Thank you.
I want you to see something.
[Shirley] We use hand signals
to communicate.
If people from the Mids join us.
we'll teach them how it works.
[metal clangs]
Hey!
Come into the light.
or we'll come drag you in.
It's me.
What are you doing here. Cooper?
Knox told me to follow you.
A fucking spy. Coop?
I figured as much.
Well. go tell him what you saw.
what we talked about.
He can't stop us.
I'm gonna tell him
you were home by curfew.
All of you were.
Why would you do that?
Because I was Juliette's shadow.
It was just us two in the generator room
when everything was going to shit.
We'd be dead if it hadn't been for her.
So I'm not here for Knox.
I'm here for Juliette.
And whatever you guys are doing.
I want in.
[sighs]
Bernard's story about the tape was a lie.
I know that Walker switched the tape
because she sent a--
[Martha] You don't know shit. girl.
You keep saying stuff like that.
we'll all be sent to the mines.
They've got eyes and ears everywhere.
How did you find us?
I followed this mastermind.
None of you are cut out
for this kind of thing.
You're no good at it. So. quit talking
about the tape and Juliette and all.
It's hazardous for your health.
Are you with us?
What are you aiming to do?
Find people like us.
People who think like us.
Who know they're being lied to.
and wanna know the truth.
When there's enough of you. what then?
We demand answers.
Yeah. you won't get answers.
Then we fight.
[Martha] They're ready for that.
You've seen all the raiders
and deputies out there.
They're just waiting for one of you
to make the first move.
- They've got all the weapons.
- Well. maybe some of the raiders
and deputies will decide
they wanna know the truth too.
M-Maybe.
Little while ago. I heard on the radio
there's some new graffiti
growing up all over the Silo.
"JL."
Juliette lives.
[Shirley] Good.
Good. because I think it's true.
I think she's alive.
What do you think. Walk?
Well. with all of you guys dedicated
to finding out the truth. yeah.
She's alive.
For the first time in 25 years.
I don't wanna be drunk.
I wanna be as clear-headed
as I can about this.
And you going forward.
I'll help you. Bernard.
Thank you. I know that together--
First. let me tell you
what you have to do for me.
I'll give you whatever you ask.
Then get me some of the good tape.
and put it aside until the crisis is over.
Why?
I want my freedom.
I don't know what--
You couldn't get me
the wizard's hot-air balloon.
so I want what Juliette Nichols had today.
I want to go out.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm